<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="development_name">Meticulus Development</string>
    <string name="extras_section_name">Extras</string>
    <string name="app_name">Codinalte Parts</string>
    <string name="kernel_header">KERNEL</string>
    <string name="venturi_variant_title">USA Variant</string>
    <string name="doubletap2wake_title">DoubleTap2Wake</string>
    <string name="sweep2wake_title">Sweep2Wake</string>
    <string name="bln_title">BLN</string>
    <string name="blnblink_title">BLN: Blink!</string>
    <string name="network_header">NETWORKING</string>
    <string name="googledns_title">Google DNS</string>
    <string name="workarounds_header">WORKAROUNDS</string>
    <string name="clockfreeze_title">Clock Freeze Monitor</string>
    <string name="incallaudio_title">In-Call Audio</string>
    <string name="bttether_title">BT Tether</string>
    <string name="h264softdec_title">H.264 SoftDec</string>
    <string name="CPU2_title">CPU2</string>
    <string name="LMKNKP_title">Low Memory Killer\nNot Killable Procs</string>
    <string name="autologcat_title">Auto logcat</string>
    <string name="autokmsg_title">Auto kmsg</string>
    <string name="autoril_title">Auto RIL log</string>
    <string name="performance_header">PERFORMANCE</string>
    <string name="debugging_header">DEBUGGING</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="venturi_variant_desc">If you have the USA or Canadian version of the YP-G70 then
    this should be on, otherwise it should be off.\n\nXAA and XAC are USA and Canadian with
    capacitive home button. All other codes are INT with the physical home button.\n\n You will have
    problems with you buttons if this is not set correctly.\n\nReboot required after switching.
    </string>
    <string name="doubletap2wake_desc">Allows you to double tap on the screen to wake up the device.
    Note: does not work in deep sleep unless a wakelock is used.</string>
    <string name="sweep2wake_desc">Allows you to swipe the screen, left to right,
    to wake up the device. Note: does not work in deep sleep unless a wakelock is
    used.</string>
    <string name="bln_desc">When you receive a notification and the screen is off the
        back-light on your capacitive buttons will illuminate. The button back-light will
        return to normal behavior after you wake the device.</string>
    <string name="blnblink_desc">Causes the button-backlights to blink when BLN is enabled.</string>
    <string name="googledns_desc">Uses dnsmasq to force the use of Google\'s DNS servers
        instead of whatever is assigned by DHCP. Only known to work with Wifi.\n\nNOTE: Disable this
        if this device is used as a tethering "server"!</string>
    <string name="clockfreeze_desc">If the status bar clock get stuck enable this.
    WARNING: Do not depend on this to fix the alarm clock. NOTE: Experimental for now.</string>
    <string name="incallaudio_desc">The In-Call Audio Service runs in the background
    and when you are on a call. It resets the volume to workaround the low-in-call volume
    problem. It also detects if you switch to speaker phone and resets the volume for that
    stream as well.</string>
    <string name="bttether_desc">The BT Tether workaround detects when your connected to
    a Tethering "server" and runs dhcp on the bt-pan interface and also runs dnsmasq
    for you automatically; effectively fixing bluetooth tethering.</string>
    <string name="h264softdec_desc">This option forces the use of the Google software decoder
    for H.264 video. This fixes issues in the latest release of the official Youtube app. However
    the switch is system wide and the Google software decoder does not work well when watching
    HD video such as video captured from the camera app.\n\nBasically: Enable to fix Youtube. Disable
    for HD video.</string>
    <string name="cpu2_desc">I am not sure what benefits this has but this allows you
    to disable the secondary cpu. It is possible that this may save battery life.
    Note: I have noticed that disabling it sometimes causes the min and max scaling
    frequency to both be set at 1000 mhz???(Experimental)</string>
    <string name="LMKNKP_desc">Low Memory Killer - Not Killable Processes: allows
    you to set a white list of processes in the LMK. LMK will not kill these
    processes when more memory is needed unless it is absolutely neccessary.</string>
    <string name="autologcat_desc">Auto logcat enables automatic dumping of the log
    to a file in the root of the sdcard. Does not clean up after itself. Should
    probably keep this off unless I ask you to turn it on.</string>
    <string name="autokmsg_desc">Auto kmsg enables automatic dumping of the kernel log
    to a file in the root of the sdcard. Does not clean up after itself. Should
    probably keep this off unless I ask you to turn it on.</string>
    <string name="autorillog_desc">Auto ril log enables automatic dumping of the Radio log
    to a file in the root of the sdcard. Does not clean up after itself. Should
    probably keep this off unless I ask you to turn it on.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_test">TestActivity</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_sposnsors">Sposnsors</string>

</resources>
