<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Codinalte Parts</string>
    <string name="clockfreeze_title">Clock Freeze Monitor</string>
    <string name="incallaudio_title">In-Call Audio</string>
    <string name="bttether_title">Bluetooth Tether</string>
    <string name="CPU2_title">CPU2</string>
    <string name="LMKNKP_title">Low Memory Killer\nNot Killable Procs</string>
    <string name="autologcat_title">Auto logcat</string>
    <string name="autokmsg_title">Auto kmsg</string>
    <string name="autoril_title">Auto RIL log</string>
    <string name="enablebln_title">Enable BLN</string>
    <string name="workarounds_header">WORKAROUNDS</string>
    <string name="performance_header">PERFORMANCE</string>
    <string name="bln_header">BACKLIGHT NOTIFICATION</string>
    <string name="debugging_header">DEBUGGING</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="clockfreeze_desc">If the status bar clock get stuck enable this.
    WARNING: Do not depend on this to fix the alarm clock. NOTE: Experimental for now.
    </string>
    <string name="incallaudio_desc">The In-Call Audio Service runs in the background
    and when you are on a call. It resets the volume to workaround the low-in-call volume
    problem. It also detects if you switch to speaker phone and resets the volume for that
    stream as well.</string>
    <string name="bttether_desc">The BT Tether workaround detects when your connected to
    a Tethering "server" and runs dhcp on the bt-pan interface and also runs dnsmasq
    for you automatically; effectively fixing bluetooth tethering.</string>
    <string name="cpu2_desc">I am not sure what benefits this has but this allows you
    to disable the secondary cpu. It is possible that this may save battery life.
    Note: I have noticed that disabling it sometimes causes the min and max scaling
    frequency to both be set at 1000 mhz???(Experimental)</string>
    <string name="LMKNKP_desc">Low Memory Killer - Not Killable Processes: allows
    you to set a white list of processes in the LMK. LMK will not kill these
    processes when more memory is needed unless it is absolutely neccessary.</string>
    <string name="autologcat_desc">Auto logcat enables automatic dumping of the log
    to a file in the root of the sdcard. Does not clean up after itself. Should
    probably keep this off unless I ask you to turn it on.</string>
    <string name="autokmsg_desc">Auto kmsg enables automatic dumping of the kernel log
    to a file in the root of the sdcard. Does not clean up after itself. Should
    probably keep this off unless I ask you to turn it on.</string>
    <string name="autorillog_desc">Auto ril log enables automatic dumping of the Radio log
    to a file in the root of the sdcard. Does not clean up after itself. Should
    probably keep this off unless I ask you to turn it on.</string>

</resources>
